Want some?
No, thanks. I'm a vegetarian.
-So?
-I don't eat animals.
-But this is beef.
-Precisely.
-Precisely what?
-It's animal meat.
It's cow meat.
-And what is a cow?
-An animal, but...
No, it's cow meat.
I don't think you get it.
Didn't you know the beef
comes from a cow?
-Come on! Seriously?
-It's obvious.
Why? Holy shit! Why?
It's beef. What did you expect?
I thought it was an expression,
not that I was eating
a fucking cow.
Ribs comes from cows too?
-Yes.
-Come on! Nobody told me?
Douches!
Cows have fur, this doesn't.
Because it comes
from inside the cow.
And how would I know
what's inside a cow?
And this beetroot juice,
what is it?
-It's blood.
-No!
-And the tongue?
-It's the tongue of a dead animal.
-No more! Have mercy! And the guts?
-That too.
And the hanger steak?
Is not from a real hanger, is it?
No.
It's the cow's belly.
I will never eat meat again
in my life.
Why don't you
order something else?
Yes, I should.
Waiter.
Do you have Nuggets?
-Ladyfingers?
-They're cake biscuits.
-And gummy bears?
-Not actual bears.
-Gummy maggots?
-Not actual maggots.
Camel balls either.
-Zombie mints?
-Made of sugar.
-And chocolate bunnies?
-Made of chocolate.
Not cold?
-I'll lend you my jacket.
-It's animal skin.
My Uber is here.
Call me.